Takin' the beat to the streets!
Beat Street is a drama, music film directed by Stan Lathan.
An aspiring DJ, from the South Bronx, and his best friend, a promoter, try to get
into show business by exposing people to hip-hop music and culture.
Kenny Kirkland, played by Guy Davis.
Tracy Carlson, played by Rae Dawn Chong.
Carmen Cararro, played by Saundra Santiago.
Himself, played by Doug E. Fresh.
Cora, played by Mary Alice.
Domingo, played by Shawn Elliott.
Beat Street is a 1984 American dance drama film featuring New
York City hip hop culture of the early 1980s.
Set in the South Bronx, the film follows the lives of a pair of brothers and their group of friends, all of whom are
devoted to various elements of early hip hop culture, including breakdancing, DJing and graffiti.
The film explores themes of dance, rap music,
hip-hop, rhyme battle, disc jockey.
The tone is emotional and intense.